{
	"test": [
		{
			"number": 1,
			"question": "Based on the passage above, what are the environmental trade-offs of hybrid electric vehicles?",
			"graphic": "Science_Quiz_3_1",
			"answers": [
				"There is only enough lanthanum available in the world to meet the demand of the Toyota Prius.",
				"While hybrid cars may reduce our dependance on fossil fuels, they may also increase our \n dependance on metals that are extracted from the ground in a destructive manner.",
				"Water near surface mining operations is highly acidic, sometimes with a pH of 2.5 or lower.",
				"Toyota obtains its lanthanum from China."
			],
			"answer": "While hybrid cars may reduce our dependance on fossil fuels, they may also increase our \n dependance on metals that are extracted from the ground in a destructive manner."
		},
		{
			"number": 2,
			"question": "Which sentence from the passage above best supports the idea that driving a hybrid electric vehicle burns gasoline?",
			"graphic": "Science_Quiz_3_1",
			"answers": [
				"'Many individuals concerned with their carbon footprint are excited about the availability of hybrid electric vehicles.'",
				"'These cars are much more effficient in their use of fossil fuels than similarly sized internal combustion automobiles.'",
				"'However, hybrid electric vehicles do come with an environmental price tag.'",
				"'Such extraction processes are a type of surface mining, which have severe environmental impacts such as erosion, \n acid mine drainage, water pollution, and disruption of habit.'"
			],
			"answer": "'These cars are much more effficient in their use of fossil fuels than similarly sized internal combustion automobiles.'"
		},
		{
			"number": 3,
			"question": "According to the formula, which of the following will result in a lower BMR?",
			"graphic": "Science_Quiz_3_2",
			"answers": [
				"Greater weight",
				"Greater height",
				"Greater age",
				"None of the above"
			],
			"answer": "Greater age"
		},
		{
			"number": 4,
			"question": "Convert this height measurement into meters:",
			"graphic": "Science_Quiz_3_3",
			"answers": [
				"1.73 meters",
				"0.173 meters",
				"0.0173 meters",
				"0.00173 meters"
			],
			"answer": "0.0173 meters"
		},
		{
			"number": 5,
			"question": "A crowbar can be used to remove a nail from a board. If the crowbar has a mechanical advantage of 8, and the a force of 40 Newtons is applied to it, what will be the output force?",
			"graphic": "Science_Quiz_3_4",
			"answers": ["5 Newtons", "320 Newtons", "0.2 Newtons", "32 Newtons"],
			"answer": "320 Newtons"
		},
		{
			"number": 6,
			"question": "In a lab experiment designed to test the rate at which plants grow under artificial light, the kind of light used is which type of variable?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["Dependent", "Independent", "Random", "Responding"],
			"answer": "Independent"
		},
		{
			"number": 7,
			"question": "After analyzing the data, what is the most appropriate conclusion about the effects of caffeine on the heart rate of healthy 20-year-old women?",
			"graphic": "Science_Quiz_3_5",
			"answers": [
				"Caffeine increases the pulse rates of women",
				"Caffeine decreases the pulse rates of women",
				"Caffiene is safe to consume",
				"Regular coffee is healthier than decaffeinated coffee"
			],
			"answer": "Caffeine increases the pulse rates of women"
		},
		{
			"number": 8,
			"question": "A student hypothesizes that eating a teaspoon of raw honey will prevent sneezing in people who are allergic to pollen. She runs an experiment to test her hypothesis. What is the dependent variable?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["Eating", "Raw Honey", "Sneezing", "Pollen"],
			"answer": "Sneezing"
		},
		{
			"number": 9,
			"question": "Which of the following changes would decrease network latency?",
			"graphic": "Science_Quiz_3_6",
			"answers": [
				"Increase distance",
				"Decrease speed",
				"Decrease packet size",
				"Decrease transmission rate"
			],
			"answer": "Decrease packet size"
		},
		{
			"number": 10,
			"question": "Purple flowers, yellow seeds and inflated seed pods are all dominant traits in pea plants. The recessive traits being white flowers, green seeds and constricted seed pods. If a plant that is homozygous dominant for flower color is crossed with a plant that is heterozygous for flower color, what percentage of the offspring will have yellow flowers?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["100%", "75%", "25%", "0%"],
			"answer": "0%"
		}
	]
}
